<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a ReqIF Model">

  <intro>
    <description>
      This cheat sheet is a step-by-step description of how to create a ReqIF
      model.
We will use the ReqIF terminology, which can be confusing. Therefore, please familiarize yourself with the terminology first (Help link).

In ReqIF terminology, a requirement is called SpecObject, a link is a SpecRelation, and the document view consists of SpecHierarchies. Confused? Then please have a look at Help link, where the terminology is described.
    </description>
  </intro>

  <item title="Set up the environment">
  	<description>
  	  Your environment must be set up before you can perform the steps in this cheat sheet.
  	  <br/><br/>
The easiest way for installing fmStudio is downloading formalmind Stu­dio. This is a standalone-application that is based on Eclipse ProR, combined with some enhancements.

Alternatively, you can install ProR in any Eclipse-Installation via its update site (listed on the RMF Download page). This is recommended for advanced users only who need to integrate RMF with other Eclipse-based components.
  	</description>
  </item>

  <item
        dialog="true"
        href="/org.eclipse.emf.doc/tutorials/clibmod/clibmod.html#newEmptyEMFProj"
        skip="true"
        title="Create an empty project">
    <description>
      If you do not already have one, create a new project: Select File | New | Project;
    </description>

    <subitem label="Select &quot;File &gt;New &gt;Project...&quot;. Expand &quot;General&quot;, select &quot;Project&quot; and click &quot;Next&quot;." skip="true">
      <action
        pluginId="org.eclipse.rmf.cheatsheets"
        class="org.eclipse.rmf.cheatsheets.handlers.CreateProjectHandler"
        translate="" />
    </subitem>

  </item>

  <item
        dialog="true"
        skip="true"
        title="Create ReqIF model">
    <description>
      Create the ReqIF model by selecting File | New | Reqif10 Model
Select the project and name the file “tutorial.reqif”. Click Finish;

Upon completion, the model will be opened, as well as the one and only Specification contained in this model.
    </description>
    <subitem label="Create the ReqIF model." skip="true">
      <action
        pluginId="org.eclipse.rmf.cheatsheets"
        class="org.eclipse.rmf.cheatsheets.handlers.CreateReqIFModelHandler"
        translate="" />
    </subitem>
  </item>



</cheatsheet>
